Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Manuscript group and University records finding aid ribbon copies, Accession 2016-A-047
  - MS 1350: Peru, computer lists sorted by imprint date, author/title, and ID number, 1984 March (Box 128)
  - MS 1350: Miscellaneous Latin America, computer lists sorted by imprint date, author/title, and ID number, 1984 July 29 (Box 129)
  - MS 1351 (3 of 4) - MS 1354, MS 1356 - MS 1368 (Box 98)
  - MS 1370 - MS 1388 (Box 99)
  - MS 1389 - MS 1409 (Box 100)
  - MS 1410 - MS 1439 (Box 101)
  - MS 1440 - MS 1471 (Box 102)
  - MS 1472, MS 1474 - MS 1499 (Box 103)
  - MS 1500 - MS 1533 (Box 104)
  - MS 1534 - MS 1567, MS 1569 - MS 1575 (Box 105)
  - MS 1576 - MS 1605 (Box 106)
  - MS 1606 - MS 1631 (Box 107)
  - MS 1632 - MS 1672 (Box 108)
  - MS 1673 - MS 1677, MS 1679 - MS 1704, MS 1706 - MS 1710 (Box 109)
  - MS 1711 - MS 1712, MS 1714 - MS 1738, MS 1740 - MS 1752 (Box 110)
  - MS 1753 - MS 1759, MS 1761 - MS 1763, MS 1765 - MS 1776 (Box 111)
  - MS 1777 - MS 1790, MS 1792 - MS 1802, MS 1804 - MS 1818, MS 1822 - MS 1826 (Box 112)
  - MS 1828 - MS 1832, MS 1834 - MS 1836, MS 1838 - MS 1841, MS 1843, MS 1845 - MS 1857 (Box 113)
  - MS 1858 - MS 1860, MS 1862 - MS 1865, MS 1868, MS 1871, MS 1875, MS 1876, MS 1978, MS 1879, MS 1883, MS 1886 (Box 114)
  - RU 11 (Box 115)
  - RU 29 (Box 115)
  - RU 31 (Box 115)
  - RU 32 (Box 115)
  - RU 33 (Box 115)
  - RU 40 (Box 115)
  - RU 41 (Box 115)
  - RU 52 (Box 115)
  - RU 53 (Box 115)
  - RU 54 (Box 115)
  - RU 62 (Box 115)
  - RU 65 (Box 115)
  - RU 66 (Box 115)
  - RU 67 (Box 115)
  - RU 68 (Box 115)
  - RU 95 (Box 115)
  - RU99 (Box 115)
  - RU 101 (Box 115)
  - RU 102 (Box 115)
  - RU 108 (Box 115)
  - RU 113 (Box 116)
  - RU 125 (1 of 3) (Box 116)
  - RU 125 (2 of 3) (Box 116)
  - RU 125 (3 of 3) (Box 116)
  - RU 126 (1 of 3) (Box 116)
  - RU 126 (2 of 3) (Box 116)
  - RU 126 (3 of 3) (Box 116)
  - RU 128 (1 of 3) (Box 117)
  - RU 128 (2 of 3) (Box 117)
  - RU 128 (3 of 3) (Box 117)
  - RU 133 (Box 117)
  - RU 135 (Box 117)
  - RU 142 (Box 117)
  - RU 158 (Box 117)
  - RU 16O (Box 117)
  - RU 161 (Box 117)
  - RU 162 (1 of 4) (Box 117)
  - RU 162 (2 of 4) (Box 118)
  - RU 162 (3 of 4) (Box 118)
  - RU 162 (4 of 4) (Box 118)
  - RU 163 (Box 118)
  - RU 164 (Box 118)
  - RU 167 (Box 118)
  - RU 172 (Box 118)
  - RU 191 (Box 118)
  - RU 204 (Box 118)
  - RU 205 (1 of 3) (Box 118)
  - RU 205 (2 of 3) (Box 118)
  - RU 205 (3 of 3) (Box 118)
  - RU 207 (Box 118)
  - RU 212 (Box 119)
  - RU 214 (Box 119)
  - RU 221 (Box 119)
  - EU 222 (Box 119)
  - RU 223 (Box 119)
  - RU 230 (Box 119)
  - RU 254 (Box 119)
  - RU 255 (Box 119)
  - RU 256 (Box 119)
  - RU 262 (Box 120)
  - RU 263 (Box 120)
  - RU 265 (Box 120)
  - RU 275 (Box 120)
  - RU 276 (1 of 2) (Box 120)
  - RU 276 (2 of 2) (Box 120)
  - RU 279 (Box 120)
  - RU 280 (Box 120)
  - RU 281 (Box 121)
  - RU 291 (Box 121)
  - RU 304 (Box 121)
  - RU 305 (Box 121)
  - RU 314 (Box 121)
  - RU 348 (Box 121)
  - RU 350 (Box 121)
  - RU 356 (Box 121)
  - RU 373 (Box 121)
  - RU 374 (Box 121)
  - RU 444 (Box 121)
  - RU 445 (Box 121)
  - RU 446 (Box 121)
  - RU 447 (Box 121)
  - RU 460 (Box 121)
  - RU 477 (Box 121)
  - RU 486 (Box 121)
  - RU 521 (Box 121)
  - RU 575 (Box 121)
  - RU 579 (Box 121)
  - RU 581 (Box 121)
  - RU 587 (1 of 3) (Box 121)
  - RU 587 (2 of 3) (Box 121)
  - RU 587 (3 of 3) (Box 122)
  - RU 592 (Box 122)
  - RU 599 (Box 122)
  - RU 726 (Box 122)
  - RU 727 (Box 122)
  - RU 728 (Box 122)
  - RU 745 (Box 122)
  - RU 756 (Box 122)
  - RU 759 (Box 122)
  - RU 782 (Box 122)
  - RU 783 (Box 122)
  - RU 788 (Box 122)
  - RU 789 (Box 122)
  - RU 790 (Box 122)
  - RU 791 (Box 122)
  - RU 795 (Box 122)
  - RU 821 (Box 122)
  - RU 832 (1 of 2) (Box 122)
  - RU 832 (2 of 2) (Box 122)
  - RU 834 (Box 123)
  - RU 843 (Box 123)
  - RU 844 (Box 123)
  - RU 846 (Box 123)
  - RU 893 (Box 123)
  - RU 913 (Box 123)
  - RU 919 (Box 123)
  - RU 922 (1 of 4) (Box 123)
  - RU 922 (2 of 4) (Box 123)
  - RU 922 (3 of 4) (Box 123)
  - RU 922 (4 of 4) (Box 123)
  - RU 932 (Box 123)
  - RU 948 (Box 123)
  - RU 978 (Box 123)
  - RU 995 (Box 123)
  - RU 1007 (Box 124)
  - RU 1011 (Box 124)
  - RU 1014 (Box 124)
  - RU 1021 (Box 124)
  - RU 1037 (Box 124)
  - RU 1048 (Box 124)
  - RU 1049 (Box 124)
  - RU 1054 (Box 124)
  - RU 1057 (Box 124)
  - RU 1074 (Box 124)
  - RU 1087 (Box 124)
  - RU 1088 (Box 124)
  - RU 1092 (Box 124)
  - RU 9000 (Box 124)
  - RU 9001 (Box 124)
  - RU 9003 (Box 124)
  - RU 9004 (Box 124)
  - RU 9005 (Box 124)
  - RU 9007 (Box 124)
  - RU 9008 (Box 124)
  - RU 9009 (Box 124)
  - RU 9010 (Box 124)
  - RU 9011 (Box 125)
  - RU 9012 (Box 125)
  - RU 9013 (Box 125)
  - RU 9014 (Box 125)
  - RU 9015 (Box 125)
  - RU 9016 (1 of 2) (Box 125)
  - RU 9016 (2 of 2) (Box 125)
  - RU 9017 (Box 125)
  - RU 9018 (Box 125)
  - RU 9019 (Box 125)
  - RU 9020 (Box 125)
- University Archives accession records, 2013-2017; Accession 2018-A-003
  - 2013-A-021 to 2016-A-046 (Box 1)
  - 2016-A-050 to 2017-A-062 (Box 2)